{
  "relevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The reported death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised from 1,833 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The reported death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The reported death toll decreased from 1,833 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised downward from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised downward from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised downward from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised downward from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised downward from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was decreased from 1,833 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was decreased from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was decreased from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    }
  ],
  "relevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was reduced by 25%",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The reported death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was reduced by 25%",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,833 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,833 to 1,247.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised downward from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised downward from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was reduced by 1,000.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The reported death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The reported death toll decreased from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The reported death toll decreased from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The reported death toll decreased from 1,833 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,836 to 1,547.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised downward from 1,836 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,836 to 1,833.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,836 to 1,833.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,836 to 1,833.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,836 to 1,577.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was decreased from 1,836 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,836 to 1,833.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,836 to 1,833.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised upward to 1,833.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised upwards to 1,836.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised upward to 1,836.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised upwards to 1,836.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised from 1,836 to 1,833.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,836 to 1,547.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised upwards to 1,836.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised upwards to 1,836.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised upwards to 1,836.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised down to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,836 to 1,547.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was revised downward from 1,836 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,836 to 1,833.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,836 to 1,833.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC revised the death toll from 1,836 to 1,833.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was unchanged.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was unchanged.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The reported death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,245.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The reported death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,346.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC did not revise the death toll of Hurricane Katrina.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was decreased from 1,836 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll remained unchanged.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The reported death toll remained unchanged.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The reported death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,346.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC did not change the death toll of Hurricane Katrina.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll decreased from 1,836 to 1,392.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC did not change the death toll of Hurricane Katrina.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The NHC did not change the death toll of Hurricane Katrina.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The death toll was decreased from 1,836 to 1,567.",
      "needle": "The reported death toll decreased to 1,392",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "In January 2023, the NHC revised the fatality data of Hurricane Katrina, what was the outcome of the reported death toll?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ]
}